-我们需要知道你所知道的
- We need to know what you know.
-那不是我的任务，我没有情报。
- It wasn't my op. I have no intel.
-未经授权。
- It wasn't authorized.
——没有。
- No.
你为什么叫我来?
Why'd you call me here?
-杰里米和凯勒消失了
- Jeremy and Caleb have disappeared.
如你所见，他们把一个线人交给了俄国人。
As you can see, they delivered an asset into the hands of the Russians.
中情局雇了安东尼·格林和他的团队来阻止他们。
CIA contracted Anthony Greene and his team to stop them.
-看起来像是埋伏。
- Reads like an ambush.
-是的，发生了枪战。
- Yeah, there was a shootout.
线人跑了。
The asset got away.
我们需要知道他们可能分享过的一切。
We need to know everything that they might have shared.
-我父亲和凯勒怎么了
- What happened to my father and Caleb?
-凯勒，他逃走了
- Caleb, he fled.
他去地下。
He went underground.
——我的父亲吗?
- My father?
-格林报告说你父亲倒下了，但他必须在其他人到达之前转移所有的伤亡人员。
- Greene reported that your father went down, but he had to remove any dead and wounded before anyone else arrived.
-他的尸体呢?
- Where's his body?
-我猜俄国人抓住他了。
- I'm assuming the Russians got him.
也许凯勒回来了。我不知道。
Perhaps Caleb came back. I don't know.
我们回来的时候现场已经干净了。
The site was clean once we arrived back.
截至昨晚18点，他们的状态在内部发生了变化。
As of 1800 hours last night, their status has been changed internally.
CIA认为他们是叛徒，现在他们的人头被悬赏。
The CIA has deemed them as traitors, and they now have a bounty on their head.
他们在这个组织的地位已经被剥夺了所有和他们共事的人现在都有问题。
Their position with this organization has been forfeited And anyone working with them is now in question.
-你是在暗示我是叛徒吗?
- Are you suggesting that I'm a traitor?
-在一段时间内，我相信你能修复被…女妖，别这样。
- Within time, I'm sure you can repair the damage that's been done by... Banshee, don't do this.
你不是国家的敌人。
You're not an enemy of the state.
-我们都知道凯勒和我父亲对这个组织很忠诚
- We both know that Caleb and my father were loyal to this organization.
-鉴于目前的情况，我不太确定。
- Well, in light of this current situation, I'm not really sure right now.
不要这样做!
Don't do this!
-把我的名字从你的账簿上划掉
- Take my name off your books.
我出去了。
I'm out.
等我查出真相，我会回来找你们这些把他们丢在外面等死的人。
And when I find out what really happened, I'll return for all of you that left them out there to fucking die.
-我控制了摄像头。
- I got control of the cameras.
你可以走了。
You're good to go.
进进出出，就像我们计划的那样。
In and out, just like we planned.
有两个人在大厅。
There'll be two in the lobby.
,还有其他的吗?——没有可见的。
- Any others? - None visible.
第二套电梯。
Second set of elevators.
你的战车已经在路上了。
And your chariot is on its way.
-他们不可能是联邦探员。
- There's no way those guys are Feds.
-显然他知道有人悬赏他的人头
- Obviously, he knows there's a price on his head.
-这家伙到底做了什么?
- What the hell did this guy do anyway?
-我是刽子手，不是法官
- I'm the executioner, not the judge.
——该死的!
- Damn it!
——科隆诺斯?- 1秒。
- Kronos? - One second.
我遇到了一些技术上的困难。
I'm having some technical difficulty.
-他们要收回吗?
- Are they taking it back?
-不不不别担心。
- No, no, no. Don't worry.
-我需要知道我是不是走进了一个陷阱?
- I need to know. Am I walking into a trap?
-不，只是个电梯。我不会担心。
- No, it's just an elevator. I wouldn't worry.
-告诉我。
- Talk to me.
-好吧，有件小事。
- All right, there's one small thing.
-没有什么是小事。
- There's no such thing as a small thing.
-我无法进入这层楼的摄像头。
- I couldn't access the camera on this floor.
- - - ?
- And?
-有人在电梯里控制我。
- Ugh, someone's overriding my control in the elevator.
——做点什么。
- Do something.
——我不能!
- I can't!
-好，好，好。
- Well, well, well.
她就在那儿。
There she is.
女妖……你还这么说吗?
Banshee... You still going with that?
——安东尼·格林。
- Anthony Greene.
已经一分钟了。
It's been a minute.
你杀了我。
You took my kill.
你让我损失了一百万美元。
You just cost me a million dollars.
——没有。
- No.
我没花你一分钱，亲爱的。
I didn't cost you a penny, sweetheart.
事实上，我会把功劳和钱都给你。
In fact, I'm going to give you the credit and the money.
你所要做的就是交出你的凯勒。
And all you have to do is hand over your boy Caleb.
天啊，你还在想这个?
Oh, man, you're still on that?
真的吗?
Really?
这有点可悲，你不觉得吗?
It's kind of sad, don't you think?
-不，我他妈不知道
- No, uh, I fucking don't.
因为我接近那混蛋的每一秒都是值得的。
'Cause every second that I get closer to that piece of shit is a second well spent.
-五年的时间对追踪一个人来说有点长，但我想复仇杀人就是复仇杀人。
- Five years is kind of a long time to track someone, but a revenge killing is a revenge killing, I guess.
——嗯。
- Uh-huh.
为了他的所作所为，我要杀了他。
For what he did, I'm going to take his life.
——嗯。
- Hmm.
我们都知道他销声匿迹了。
We both know he's off the grid.
他是个该死的鬼。
He's a fucking ghost.
-是啊，他是个该死的鬼。
- Yeah, he's a fucking ghost.
所以你才是找到他的最佳人选。
That's why you're the perfect person to track him down.
-如果我不了解你，我会觉得你太娘娘腔了，不会跟我一对一的。
- If I didn't know any better, I would think that you're too big of a pussy to take me on one-on-one.
——哦。
- Oh.
你他妈闭嘴。
Shut the fuck up.
我不是来玩的。
I ain't come here to play.
女妖，想想办法。
Banshee, do some thinking.
因为说到底，我们都知道结局会怎样。
'Cause end of the day, we both know how this shit's going to end.
不是吗?
Don't we?
——我做的。
- I do.
克罗诺斯，开门!
Kronos, open the door!
-打开电梯门。
- Opening elevator doors.
——走吧!
- Go!
——科隆诺斯!——我在!
- Kronos! - I'm trying!
明白了。
Got it.
——步行式。她在下来的路上。
- Walkie. She's on her way down.
你听到了吗?她在下来的路上。
Do you hear me? She's on her way down.
移动,移动,移动。
Move, move, move.
-我想我们拿不到那100万了
- I take it we're not getting that 1 million.
,而不是现在。
- Not now.
-我真的需要那笔钱。
- I really needed that money.
门就要开了。你准备好了吗?
Door's about to open. Are you ready?
-来吧。
- Fucking bring it.
有多少?
How many?
-两个在大厅。安东尼在行动。
- Two in the lobby. Anthony's on the move.
我在试图阻止他。
I'm trying to stop him.
-克罗诺斯，马上开车!——完成。
- Kronos, start the car now! - Done.
什么?
What?
所以这一切都是一个人造成的。
So one person did all of this to us.
她在跟谁说话?
Who was she talking to?
-她叫他克洛诺斯。-继续。
- She called him Kronos. - Go on this.
我要知道他是谁，在哪里。
I wanna know who he is, where he is.
我要亲手抓住他。
I want my hands on him.
把这里收拾干净。
Clean this shite up.
-那很有趣，女妖。
- Well, that was fun, Banshee.
-哥们，我告诉过你千万次了，别那样叫我。
- Dude, I've told you ten million times do not call me that.
-你怎么认识安东尼·格林的?
- How do you know Anthony Greene?
-他曾是特种部队的一员，他的人生目标是为中央情报局追捕人。
- He's former Special Forces who's made it his goal in life to hunt down people for the CIA.
-所以他是集体的一员而你想让他死?
- So he's part of the Collective and you want him dead?
-他杀了一个和我很亲近的人
- He killed someone who's close to me.
-如果他是刺客，为什么会有这么多人?
- If he's an assassin, why does he have so many guys?
-因为他是个娘们，他知道我会杀了他。
- Because he's a fucking pussy, and he knows I would kill him.
我需要你帮我找个人。
I need you to find someone for me.
-这就是我来这里的原因。
- That's what I'm here for.
-找到Caleb Navvaro
- Find Caleb Navvaro.
你是认真的吗?
- Are you serious?
迦勒Navvaro吗?这是我们的目标?
Caleb Navvaro? That's our target?
——是的。
- Yes.
-我们说的是同一个凯勒·纳瓦罗?
- We're talking about the same Caleb Navvaro?
那个训练你并负责秘密行动的人?
The one that trained you and ran black ops?
-就是这个。
- That's the one.
-迪，有一千个人叫凯勒·纳瓦罗。
- D, there's a thousand people named Caleb Navvaro.
如果格林找不到他，我也不可能。
If Greene couldn't find him, there's no way I will.
他已经在地下工作五年了。
He's been underground for five years.
我们刚刚损失了一大笔钱。
And we just lost out on a whole lot of money.
我们能谈下一个合同吗?
Can we please just move on to the next contract?
-我们不会再打安东尼了。
- We will not have another shot at Anthony.
你是认真的吗?这是你和一支小军队的对决。
- Are you serious? It's you versus a small army.
请。
Please.
-我不会再让他赢了
- I'm not letting him win again.
-你看过照片了。告诉过你他死了。
- You've seen the photographs. Told you he's dead.
听着，周末前把钱存到我的账户上。
Listen, I want our money in my account by the end of the week.
——先生?
- Sir?
-不，和往常一样，是一百万。
- No, as usual, it's a million.
是的,当然。
Yeah, sure.
是的，很高兴见到你。
Yeah, always a pleasure.
什么?-我有克罗诺斯的线索了。
What? - I've a lead on Kronos.
- - - ?——一流的黑客。
- And? - Top-rate hacker.
为女妖做中间人。
Acts as a middle man for Banshee.
显然，这几年他一直是她的耳目。
Apparently, he's been her eyes and ears for a few years.
-那他在哪里?
- So where is he?
-我还不知道。
- I don't know yet.
-那就在日出之前找到他
- So find him, and before sun up.
-好吧，让我们看看中央情报局怎么说。
- All right, let's see what the CIA has to say.
-如果他们知道什么，他早就死了，我们也不会有这次谈话了。
- If they knew anything, he'd be dead, and we would not be having this conversation.
-是关于叛徒的事吗?
- Is this about the traitor thing?
-除了其他事情，是的。
- Amongst other things, yes.
-这家伙的人头要价一千万。
- The price on this guy's head is 10 million.
——我知道。
- I know.
-你也没杀他为什么?
- And you didn't kill him. Why?
-你不明白。
- You don't understand.
对我来说，格林和凯勒比一千万值钱多了。
Greene and Caleb are worth so much fucking more to me than 10 mil.
——好的。
- All right.
你会说你比任何人都了解他吗?
Would you say you knew him better than anyone?
——是的。
- Yes.
肯定。
Definitely.
-他肯定在某个时候出了差错，分享了一些可能会帮助我们的信息。
- He had to slip up at some point, shared some kind of info that could help us.
如果你是凯勒，你会去哪里?
If you were Caleb, where would you go?
他来自芝加哥。他会回去吗?
He's from Chicago. Would he go back?
-不不不不不，不，绝对不是。
- Nah, nah, nah, nah. No, no, definitely not.
他在那里会得到太多的关注。
He'd gain too much attention there.
-最喜欢的度假地点，朋友，家人什么的，让我们…我们来做点什么。
- Favorite vacation spots, friends, family, something, let's... let's work with something here.
——Wellburg。检查Wellburg。
- Wellburg. Check Wellburg.
-韦堡在哪里?——球衣。
- Where the hell is Wellburg? - Jersey.
-好吧，有一些房子是五年前买的。
- All right, there's a few homes that were purchased five years ago.
一些企业也开放了。
Some businesses opened up too.
Barb的硬件。我们有一家意大利餐厅。
Barb's Hardware. We have an Italian place.
有个酒吧叫老井酒馆。
And there's a bar named Old Well Tavern.
够了，够了!
That's it, that's it!
Old Well酒馆，就这样。
Old Well Tavern, that's it.
-老井酒馆，老板是Walter Herrero
- Old Well Tavern, It's owned by Walter Herrero.
看来埃雷罗先生三年前买了这栋房子和酒吧。
Looks like Mr. Herrero bought the house and bar about three years ago.
低调两年，开始新生活。
Lay low for two years, start a new life.
这是他妈的他。带我去那儿。
That's fucking him. Take me there.
—更新GPS。
- Update the GPS.
这就是我所说的游戏。
This is what I call a game.
真正会打球的球员。
Players who can actually play.
-这是重播，瑞克
- It's a rerun, Rick.
——仍然。
- Still.
你知道我在说什么吧?
You know what I'm saying, right?
我们的队伍没办法保持健康，我们的牛棚烂透了。
Our team can't stay healthy, and our bullpen sucks.
——啊。
- Ugh.
我认为这种情况短期内不会改变。
I can't see that changing any time soon.
想象一下如果我们有像他们那样的好投手。
Imagine if we got some decent pitching like those guys.
——嗯。
- Hmm.
-我们会成为一个值得对抗的俱乐部。
- We'd be a ball club worth playing against.
啊!另一个镜头。
Ah! Another shot.
你的主队是哪支来着?
What was the, uh, home team where you come from again?
拉雷多,对吧?
Laredo, right?
-河对岸的新拉雷多
- Nuevo Laredo, across the river.
你在那里也开酒馆吗?
Do you run a tavern there too?
-你总是在早上10点喝这么多?
- You always drink this much at 10:00 a.m.?
——科隆诺斯?
- Kronos?
我在这里。
I'm here.
-你今天早上好吗?
- How are you this morning?
-可能比你强。你开了一整晚车吗?
- Probably better than you are. Did you drive all night?
-不，我在一个矮矮的…一些忧郁的…天啊，克罗诺斯，来吧。
- No, I stopped at some dumpy... Some dumpy... Gee, Kronos, come on, man.
-好吧，我来了。
- All right, I'm here.
我在这里。
I'm here.
-总之，我在一个脏兮兮的地方停了下来，洗了个澡，睡了一会儿。
- Anyway, so I stopped at some dumpy place, and I had a shower and a little bit of sleep.
——小假期。
- Little vacation.
——闭嘴。
- Shut up.
-你快成功了。
- You're almost there.
——我知道。
- I know.
我想跟你说件事。
There's something I wanna talk to you about.
这是我的私事，所以我要下线直到我和凯勒解决问题。
This is kind of a personal matter, so I'm gonna go offline until I sort things out with Caleb.
-别抱怨我。我终于有一天休息了。
- No complaints with me. I finally get a day off.
-很高兴知道。
- Good to know.
我们在另一边见，我的朋友。
I'll see you on the other side, my friend.
祝成功,女妖。
- Godspeed, Banshee.
-别他妈这么叫我
- Don't fucking call me that.
——嗯!
- Mmm!
你真是个混蛋，你知道吗?
You're a real asshole, you know that?
我一直来这里的唯一原因是因为我妻子是个贱人，而你营业早。
The only reason I keep coming back here is because my wife's a bitch and you open early.
-至少你回来了。——是的。
- Well, at least you come back. - Yes.
——是的。
- Yes.
——对不起。
- Sorry.
不，是我的错。
No, it was my fault.
应该道歉的人是我。
I'm the one who should be sorry.
别告诉别人，拿上酒走人。
And between me and you, get your drinks and leave.
老板真是个怪人。
The owner is a real crank.
-他一直都是这样。
- He's always been that way.
是的。
Yeah.
-还有其他人吗?
- Anybody else here?
早上很安静。
- Mornings are quiet.
你后面有个门闩。
There is a latch right behind you.
你知道该怎么做。
You know what to do.
-我猜你想把这些拿下来?
- I assume you want these down?
——确定。
- Sure.
迦勒,不喜欢。
- Caleb, don't.
-我必须去。
- I have to.
和你也一样。
And you too.
只是缓慢。
Just slowly.
这很好。
That's good.
-我也很高兴见到你。
- It's great to see you too.
是的。
Yeah.
-你怎么找到我的?
- How did you find me?
-你说过有一天你会买下这个地方的。
- You said you were going to buy this place someday.
——嗯。
- Hmm.
-你喝醉了，但是…——什么?——真诚。
- You were drunk, but... - What? - Sincere.
-你记得吗?
- You remember that?
-我不是来杀你的
- I'm not here to kill you.
——好的。
- Okay.
那么我的价格是多少呢?
So what is my price anyway?
4mil还是5mil ?
4 mil, 5 mil?
- 10。
- Ten.
-嗯，感觉不错。
- Well, that feels pretty good.
-它是，呃…如果你不听我的，我就收钱。
- And it's, uh... it's gonna get collected if you don't listen to me.
安东尼·格林在追杀你。
Anthony Greene is gunning for you.
他抢在我前面伏击我给我一百万让我放弃你。
He, uh, beat me to a job and ambushed me... and offered me a mil to give you up.
-所以你放弃了我
- So you gave me up.
-你以为我是谁?
- Who do you think I am?
-我好多年没见过你了，所以我不知道。
- I haven't seen you in years, so I don't know.
-那是谁的错?
- And whose fault is that?
这次我不会让他跑了。
I am not gonna let him get away this time.
我一个人对付不了他的军队。
And I can't handle his army alone.
-看起来我…我把你训练得很好。
- It looks like I... I trained you well.
所以…
So...
嘿，探员，别动!
Hey, Suit, don't move!
-那个黑头发的女孩是谁?
- Who's the girl with the black hair?
-她是我女儿。——你什么?
- She's my daughter. - Your what?
-是的。海利,她很好。
- Yeah. Hailey, she's fine.
-她是谁?
- Who is she?
-她是我工作上的老朋友
- Uh, she's an old friend from work.
-你是人质吗?
- Are you a hostage?
——不!不。
- No! No.
别再拿枪指着我们的客人了，好吗?
Just stop pointing your gun at our guest, right?
-你得好好解释一下。
- You have a lot of explaining to do.
-是的。
- Yeah.
海莉，这是黛利拉。
Well, you know, Hailey, this is, uh, Delilah.
Hailey大利拉。
Delilah, Hailey.
来吧，给我。
Come on, give me that.
准备好失去你所拥有的一切吧，Dogmom93。
- Get ready to lose everything you own, Dogmom93.
♪不要和我说话♪
- ♪ Don't talk to me ♪
♬不要和我说话♬
♪ Don't talk to me ♪
♪我什么都没有了
- ♪ I have nothing left ♪
啊,该死的!
Ah, damn it!
她很好。
She's good.
♪我告诉过你没有♪
- ♪ I told you no ♪
♬你的机会是……♪
♪ Your chance is... ♪
嗯。
Hmm.
喂?
Hello?
-克罗诺斯，这里有藏枪吗?
- Kronos, are there any guns hidden in here?
如果有的话我们会找到的，所以…为了方便你自己，告诉我们吧。
We're gonna find them if there are, so... make things easier for yourself and tell us.
-我总是在披萨盒里放一把左轮手枪。
- I always keep a revolver in the pizza box.
——嗯。
- Hmm.
——科隆诺斯。
- Kronos.
坨屎。
What a shithole.
你是个赌徒，是吗?
So you're a gambler, huh?
这是昂贵的。
That's expensive.
你曾经赢了?
You ever won?
-我今天运气不好。
- Not my lucky day.
——嗯。
- Eh.
我不会这么说。
I wouldn't say that.
然而。
Yet.
这就是你的生活吗?
So this is how you live, huh?
电脑和他妈的植物。
Computers and fucking plants.
植物不会顶嘴的。
- Plants don't talk back.
-克罗诺斯，也许这边更舒服些。
- Kronos, perhaps over here would be more comfortable.
——好的。
- Okay.
-你认识我一直在找的那个人，对吧?
- So you know the man I've been looking for, don't ya?
不。
No.
我有预感你知道他他妈的在哪。
Well, I got a hunch that you know exactly where the fuck he is.
不。
No.
如果你不知道他在哪，也许女妖知道。
Well, if you don't know where he is, maybe Banshee does.
我确定你知道她在哪里。
And I know for sure you know where she is.
我是来给你点东西的。
I'm here to offer you something.
有……是一百万美元。
That there... is a million dollars.
现在，你通常拿多少?
Now, what's your usual cut?
20%的可能?
20% maybe?
看看这家伙的蛋蛋。
Look at the balls on this guy.
告诉他。
Tell him.
-你的真名是迈克尔·谢伊·汤姆森。
- Your real name's Michael Shea Thomson.
你毕业于麻省理工学院，获得了计算机科学学位，然后加入了国土安全部，在那里你每时每刻都在防止俄罗斯的网络攻击。
You graduated from MIT with a degree in computer science before joining the Department of Homeland Security, where you spent every waking moment preventing Russian cyberattacks.
直到你意识到承包合同可以赚更多的钱，然后做出转变。
That is, until you realized there's more money in contracting and made the switch.
-他认识我。
- He knows me.
-是的，我们认识你。
- Yeah, we know you.
你的父母都死了。
Your mom and dad are dead.
我找不到一个爱你的人让我害怕和伤害。
And I can't find anyone who loves you that I can terrify and hurt.
所以…我要杀了你，然后自己去找女妖吗?
So... do I just kill you and then find Banshee on my own?
没有?
No?
嗯，那有点方便，因为我不太懂电脑。
Well, that's kinda handy 'cause I'm not much of a computer guy.
但这个房间里的这四个人非常非常擅长伤害别人。
But these four people in this room are very, very good at hurting people.
他们会伤害你好几个小时。
And they will hurt you for hours.
我还得让你活着吗?
Now, do I have to keep you alive?
不客气。
Not at all.
我方便吗?
Is it convenient for me?
也许吧。
Maybe.
-我想管理你的合同。
- I wanna run your contracts.
我想做你的眼睛和耳朵。
I wanna be your eyes and your ears.
我想做你的新网络男。
I wanna be your new cyber guy.
-我为什么要那么做?
- Why would I do that?
-因为我可以给你女妖。
- 'Cause I can give you Banshee.
让我们做个交易。
Let's make this deal.
-给我女妖，就给我凯勒
- You give me Banshee, you give me Caleb.
但如果你想上我，我会找到你的。
But if you try and fuck me, son, I'll find ya.
-你妈妈是画家吗?
- Is your mom a painter?
——是。
- Was.
她死了。
She's dead.
-南希四年前被诊断出癌症。
- Nancy got diagnosed with cancer four years ago.
她……她在我们搬到这里的几个月前去世了。
She... she died a few months before we moved here.
——我很抱歉。
- I'm sorry.
是的。
Yeah.
-如果她是你朋友，她怎么会不知道妈妈的事?
- If she's your friend, then how does she not know about Mom?
——嗯,我们……我们……事实上，我们没有那么亲密。
- Well, we... we... we weren't that close, actually.
-你在开玩笑吧?
- Are you kidding?
-你们在说什么?
- What are you guys talking about?
-你爸爸和我爸爸关系很好，所以我们一起长大。
- Your dad and my dad were very close, so we grew up together.
-你爸爸是建筑工吗?
- Was your dad in construction?
-我们一起在建筑工地工作。
- We worked into... In construction together.
-是啊，有段时间…我们会处在某种危险的地方…-是啊，就像我们要建摩天大楼，要互相扶持一样。
- Yep, well, there was a time... we'd be in some kind of danger spots and... - Yeah, like when we had to build skyscrapers and had to have each other's backs.
-这些和不知道妈妈有什么关系?
- What does any of that have to do with not knowing about Mom?
——嗯…好久不见了，海莉，真的。
- Well... it's been a long time, Hailey, really.
是的。
Yeah.
-她知道我们在哪
- Well, she knows where we are.
她知道黑帮的事吗?Hailey,足够了。
Does she know about the mob? - Hailey, enough.
你没有作业要做吗?没有电视节目要看吗?
Don't you have some homework to do or a show to watch on television?
——好。——好。
- Fine. - Good.
-我上楼去。
- I'll go upstairs.
——谢谢。
- Thank you.
嘿,我很抱歉。我…好吧。好吧。
Hey, I'm sorry. I'm... okay. All right.
——晚安。
- Good night.
建筑工人?
Construction worker?
真的吗?
Really?
你有那么多选择，却选了建筑工人?
Out of all the options that you had, you went with construction worker?
-是的。
- Yeah.
大城市的建筑工地可能会与肮脏的人纠缠在一起，这给了我一个搬到小城镇的理由。
Construction sites in big cities can get tangled with dirty people, giving me a reason to move to a small town.
所以建设。
So construction.
-所以你在躲避黑帮?
- Ah, so you're hiding from the mob?
这就说得通了，为什么她拿着枪跟我打招呼。
Makes sense, why she said hello at gunpoint.
你还训练她对抗黑帮。
Oh, and you're training her to fight the mob.
这很有趣，因为这和你训练我的方式很相似。
Well, it's interesting because it's very similar to how you trained me.
是的。
Yeah.
你想谈谈安东尼的事。
So you wanted to talk about Anthony.
——是的。——嗯。
- Yes. - Mm-hmm.
-那晚他和你还有我父亲在一起吗?
- Was he there that night with you and my father?
-不不不不我的过去结束了，嗯?
- No, no, no, no. We're done with my past, eh?
我们说的是安东尼。
We're talking about Anthony.
-这与你的过去无关
- This isn't about your past.
你是…你是我的良师益友。
You are... You were such an amazing mentor for me.
我需要你。
And I need you.
我真的。
I really do.
我需要你的帮助。
I need your help.
-你的问题都是问安东尼的。
- You know, all your questions are for Anthony.
是的，他在那儿。
Yeah, he was there.
-他是一个人吗?
- Was he alone?
他带人来了吗?
Did he bring anyone?
-重要吗?
- Does it matter?
——没有。
- No.
-所以你要和小斯大林打?
- So you're gonna fight Stalin Jr.?
——没有。——哦。
- No. - Oh.
-我们要一起对抗他。
- We are going to fight him together.
难道你不想停止躲藏吗?
Don't you wanna stop hiding?
-不能改变过去。
- Can't change the past.
我很好。
I am fine.
我在这里很好。
I'm fine right here.
-你怎么了?
- What happened to you?
-你知道，我…我希望你父亲和你一样在这里。
- You know, I... I wish your father was here as much as you do.
我知道一个人是什么感觉。
I know what it feels like to be alone.
生活不仅仅是雇凶杀人。
There is more to life than just contract killing.
我现在很高兴。
I'm happy now.
就在此时此地，是的。
Right here, right now, yes.
-我为你的幸福感到高兴。
- Well, I'm happy for your happiness.
——谢谢。
- Thank you.
但是,嗯…我不会做你的诱饵。
But, um... I am not gonna be your bait.
-嘿，这招不错。
- Hey, it was a good move.
-你把我教得很好
- Well, you taught me well.
等一等。
Hold on.
关于你父亲的文件在后面两份。
The files on your dad are two in back.
-晚安，女妖。
- Good night, Banshee.
——谢谢。
- Thank you.
——欢迎你。
- You're welcome.
-玛丽亚，这位是纳瓦罗先生。
- Malia, this is Mr. Navvaro.
他是我和我们组织的朋友。
He's a friend of myself and our organization.
——嗯…玛丽亚小姐,我……我知道，你父亲是个很有权势的人。
- Uh... Miss Malia, I... I understand, uh, your father is, uh, is a powerful man.
-你知道他是谁
- You know who he is.
——我做的。
- I do.
我想知道你是谁。
I would like to know who you are.
我还想知道你从这整件事中得到了什么?
And I also would like to know what do you get out of this whole thing?
——保护。我只想要保护。
- Protection. All I want is protection.
——但,是的。
- But, yeah.
但你不能因为你父亲是个亿万富翁就得到保护。
But you don't get protection just because your father is a billionaire.
你知道我不能同意。
You know I can't grant it.
-在驱动器上只是一个味道。
- On that drive is just a taste.
客户，交易，但最重要的是，大多数政府都不知道的武器设计图。
Customers, transactions, but most important, blueprints to weapons most governments don't even know about.
政府，带着他偷来的所有秘密，向前飞跃了十年。
The government, with all the secrets he's stolen, takes a leap forward by ten years.
——正确的。
- Right.
-都在那儿。-我想是的。
- It's all there. - I'm sure it is.
或者都是假的，你只是在陷害我们。
Or it's all fake and you're just, uh, setting us up.
-我才不管你们怎么想。
- I don't care what you suits think.
我给你他所有买家的名字和他所有武器的位置，我就能得到保护。
I get you the names of all his buyers and the locations of all his weapons, and I get protection.
他是个怪物，我要你把我藏得离他越远越好。
He's a monster, and I need you to hide me as far away from him as you can.
——正确的。
- Right.
我去打几个电话。
I'll make some calls, yeah.
早上好。
Good morning.
嗯。
Hmm.
-事情就是这样。
- So that's what happened.
我知道它。
I knew it.
我知道，我知道，我知道。
I knew it, I knew it, I knew it.
我就知道。
I fucking knew it.
我的爸爸在哪里?
Where's my dad?
——继续前进。你知道什么都没变。
- Move on. You know nothing has changed.
什么都没有。
Nothing.
-他们没有找到他的尸体
- They didn't recover his body.
他可能还逍遥法外。
He could still be out there.
-女妖，我看见他倒下了。
- Banshee, I saw him go down.
-但他们没找到他
- But they didn't find him.
他可能还逍遥法外。
He could still be out there.
你知道吗，我昨天告诉你了，那是…-这是问安东尼的问题。
- You know, I-I-I told you yesterday, that's, uh... - That's a question for Anthony.
——早上好。
- Good morning.
-我打扰到什么了吗?
- Am I interrupting something?
-哦,不。
- Uh, no.
就是喝杯咖啡而已。
Just, uh, having a cup of coffee.
说到这个，我该走了。
Speaking of which, uh, I should be going.
啊。
Ugh.
D，如果有什么事就给酒馆打电话。
D, call the tavern if anything comes up.
-这个酒吧有一个前门和一个后门，通向一个停车场。
- The pub has a front and a back door that leads to a parking lot.
这是很简单的。
It's pretty straightforward.
-凯勒一点都不坦率
- There's nothing straightforward about Caleb.
房子呢?
What about the house?
-被树林包围的死胡同。
- Dead-end streets surrounded by woods.
-女妖可能在那里。
- Banshee's probably there.
也就是说凯勒知道你要来
That means Caleb knows that you're coming.
——我们要来吗?
- We're coming?
你不去吗?
Are you not going?
-天啊，你知道吗?
- Oh, Jesus Christ, you know what?
你想再问我一次吗?
You want to question me again?
请。
Please.
我需要再找一个助手吗?
Do I need to find another assistant?
多久?
How long?
- 6个小时左右
- Um, six hours or so.
打电话给费城队。
Call the Philly team.
-你在想什么?
- What are you thinking?
——两个团队。
- Two teams.
一个占领房子，一个占领酒馆。
One takes the house, one takes the tavern.
他们一小时内就能到。
They can be there within the hour.
告诉去老井的队员们，要低调，要安静。
And tell the team that goes to the Old Well, you know, be subtle, be quiet.
迦勒是聪明。这可能都是不可能的。
Caleb is smart. It may all be for not.
告诉他们就位后给我发短信。
Tell them to text me when they're in position.
——明白了。
- Got it.
提醒他们我要活捉他
- And remind them I want him alive.
活蹦乱跳，因为他是我的。
Alive and kicking 'cause he's mine.
你明白了吗?——明白了。
You got it? - Got it.
-那就赶紧打电话
- So make the damn call.
你，给我找个外卖。我饿死了。
You, find me a take-away. I'm starving.
-好吧，我们15点出发。
- All right, so we head out at 1500.
不早不晚。
No sooner, no later.
无论如何不要走主干道。
Stay off the main road at all cost.
我们不希望宴会上有不速之客。
We wouldn't want any uninvited guest during the party.
现在，当我们到达市郊时，我们遇到了麻烦。
Now, when we reach the outskirts of town, we hit dirt.
现在都是越野直到我们在七公里外找到一个旧包装厂。
Now, all off-road until we find an old packing house about seven clicks out.
在那里，移交给中央情报局的工作发生了。
There, the handoff to the CIA happens.
男女特工，他们会将玛利亚和她的车保护性拘留。
Male and female agents, they will take Malia and her drives into protective custody.
好吗?幸福吗?
Good? Happiness?
好了，喝点咖啡，睡个午觉，准备好。
All right, so get some coffee, take a nap, and be ready.
——杰里米等。-这是什么?
- Jeremy, wait. - What is it?
-听起来不错，Navvaro先生。
- This all sounds great, Mr. Navvaro.
但是呢?
But?
-但是没有备用方案。
- But there's no Plan B.
-这是例行行动。
- This is a routine op.
我们做过几百次了，我相信我的人，相信我。
We have done it hundreds of times, and I trust my men, believe me.
-看来你对我父亲的人采取了一切预防措施，他们现在肯定在外面找我。
- Seems as though you've taken every precaution against my father's men, who are definitely out there hunting for me right now.
但你对自己的人毫无防备。
But you've taken no precautions against your own men.
-玛丽亚，容我说一句，随着交接的临近，有点紧张甚至偏执是正常的。
- Malia, if I may, it is normal to be a little nervous or even paranoid as we get closer to the handoff.
——这是. .,但是……-偏执还是粗心更理性?
- Is it.. - But... - More rational to be paranoid or careless?
我在这里冒着生命危险。
I am risking everything being here.
你不知道如果他抓到我，会对我做什么。
You have no idea what he'll do to me if he catches me.
我已经履行了我的承诺，我希望你也这样做。
I've held up my end of the bargain, and I expect you to do the same.
——我们。
- We are.
你见过我要移交给谁的探员吗?
Have you met the agents I'm being handed off to?
——当然。
- Of course.
他们是有最高权限的中情局特工。
They are CIA agents with top clearance.
-中情局一直是最值得信赖的机构。
- The CIA's always been the most trustworthy organization.
-让我们做我们的工作，玛丽亚。
- Let us do our job, Malia.
六个月后，你想住哪儿就住哪儿想做什么就做什么。
In six months, you will be living wherever you want and doing whatever the fuck you want.
相信我,好吗?
Trust me, okay?
好吧。
Okay.
-嘿，没关系。
- Hey, it's okay.
-曾经是我的最爱之一。
- Used to be one of my favorites.
——用于?
- Used to?
-知道结局的回忆就糟透了。
- Memories suck when you know how they end.
你是怎么想的?
So what's your deal?
——我的交易?
- My deal?
-你是来找我爸爸帮忙的，但你什么都没做，只吃和盯着我家人的照片看。
- You came here to get my dad's help, but you haven't done anything but eat and stare at photos of my family.
你们是情人吗?
Were you lovers or something?
不。
No.
我七岁时就认识他了。
I've known him since I was seven.
-他有危险吗?
- Is he in danger?
听着，我知道他和黑帮在一起很危险。
Look, I know he's in danger with the mob.
我看了桌子上你的档案。
I looked at your file on the table.
你是政府还是什么?
Are you with the government or something?
-你不应该那样做的。
- You shouldn't have done that.
——我很抱歉。我没办法。
- I'm sorry. I couldn't help it.
我觉得他有危险，他是我唯一的亲人。
I feel like he's in danger, and he is all I have left.
如果他有危险，我得知道，因为我不会让任何事…——停止!
Hey, if he's in danger, I need to know, because I will not let anything... - Stop!
我是来帮你的。
I'm here to help you.
现在，告诉我你知道的一切。
Now, tell me everything that you know.
坐下。
Sit.
-强硬，但安静的酒吧老板。
- Tough, but quiet bar owner.
爱死它了。
Love it.
我们先喝三杯啤酒。
Let's start with, uh, three beers.
——确定。
- Sure.
好吧。
All right.
-还有菜单。
- And some menus.
-哦，对不起，但是，呃，厨师病了。
- Oh, I'm sorry, but, uh, the cook is sick.
-那好吧。
- That's fine then.
实际上,我们庆祝。
We're celebrating, actually.
——好的。
- All right.
-是的，我儿子要结婚了。
- Yep, my son's getting married.
——哦,哇。
- Oh, wow.
没人说婚礼地点会像威尔堡。
Well, nothing says wedding destination like Wellburg.
啊!
Ah!
-他在这里长大。-是的。
- He grew up here. - Yeah.
-这就像是在他迈出人生的下一步之前的最后一点怀旧之情。
- It's like one last bit of nostalgia before he takes that next big step in life.
-嘿，你知道吗，你看起来比他开心。
- Hey, you know, you seem happier about it than he is.
-我能说什么呢?
- Ah, what can I say?
我猜他知道自己在做什么。
Guess he knows what he's getting himself into.
是的,这是真的。
Yeah, it's true.
对不起,先生们。
Excuse me, gentlemen.
-他们就位了。——好。
- They're in position. - Good.
放手去做吧。
Give them the go.
让另一队去搜房子。
And tell the other team to hit the house.
确保他们找到我的任何把柄，在我到达之前保证他的生命安全。
And make sure they find anything they may have on me, and to keep him alive until I get there.
-我没怎么读。
- I didn't read much of it.
我只看到了尸体的照片还有像核密码之类的流行语。
I just saw pictures of bodies and buzz words like nuclear codes.
人们会来这里吗?
Are people coming here?
——是的。
- Yes.
-我们该怎么办?
- What are we gonna do?
这是我的爸爸。
It's my dad.
——嘿,宝贝。
- Hey, Baby.
你看，我忘了告诉你修理工要来了。
You see, I forgot to tell you that the repairman is coming by.
——它们在这里。
- They're here.
-好的，我会尽快赶到的。
- Yeah, I'll be there as soon as I can, yeah.
是啊，替我亲一下宝宝。
Uh, yeah, give a kiss to the baby for me.
——我会的。——谢谢。再见。
- I will. - Thank you. Bye.
-把枪拿来。
- Get your gun.
现在!
Now!
-诚实…我见过更糟的。
- Honestly... I have seen worse.
我是说，你演得非常好，非常好。
I mean, you were very good, very good.
但这两个吗?
But these two?
它们就像湿毛巾一样。
They preform like wet towels.
——三个入口。还有其他的吗?
- Three entrances. Any others?
-地下室入口从大厅出来。
- Basement entrance comes out down the hall.
海莉，我要你上楼，把自己锁在房间里。
- Hailey, I want you to go upstairs, lock yourself in your room.
在我说安全之前不要出来。
And do not come out until I say it's clear.
-我不会丢下你一个人的
- I'm not leaving you alone.
Hailey,走吧!
- Hailey, go!
-放开我!
- Let me go!
——下车!起来!
- Get off! Get up!
——别担心。
- Don't worry.
你走后我会照顾你女儿的。
I'll take care of your girl when you're gone.
-嗨。
- Hey.
婴儿。
Baby.
嘿,宝贝。
Hey, baby.
嗯…嘿…她需要知道真相在她听到谎言之前。
Um... hey... she needs to know the truth... before she hears lies.
——是的。
- Yes.
-很抱歉我之前没有告诉你。
- I'm so sorry I didn't tell you this before.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
-没事，没事，没事。
- It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
——嗯,是吗?
- Hmm, yeah?
我，你知道，我训练过你。
I, you know, I have trained you.
你要听……到D，对吧?
And you have to listen to... To D now, all right?
你理解我吗?
You understand me?
——我明白了。
- I understand.
-你明白我的意思…好,好。
- You understand what I'm trying... good, good.
隐藏她的。
Hide her.
——我会的。
- I will.
-你知道他们想要她，对吧?
- You know they want her, right?
——是的。
- Yes.
-嘿，宝贝，你…你是我生命中最美好的事。
- Hey, Baby, you're... you're the best thing that ever happened to me.
-有房子的那队怎么说?
- What's the word on the team that had the house?
-没什么。
- Not a thing.
-好吧，他们死了。
- Okay, they're dead.
-我是说，也许他们只是在等…-不，他们死了。
- I mean, maybe they're just waiting... - Nah, they're dead.
那些侦察员呢?
What about the spotters?
-他们已经就位了
- They're in position now.
凯勒的车在那里，但没有他和女妖的踪迹。
Caleb's car's there, but no sign of him or Banshee.
-所以他们躲在房子里等我们
- So they're holed up in the house waiting for us.
你听到什么?
What're you hearing?
-我们三个人死在酒馆里了
- Our three are dead inside the tavern.
-有什么能把他们和我们联系起来的吗?
- And is there anything to link them back to us?
-警察认为是抢劫出了差错
- Cops think it was a robbery gone wrong.
他们正在寻找失主。
They're trying to find the owner.
-我们还要多久才能得到支援?
- How long before we get some backup?
-又有一队人从城里过来了。
- There's another team coming from the city now.
他们三小时后到。
They'll be here in three hours.
-让他们快点
- Ugh, make sure they hustle.
我要这些混蛋。
I want these assholes.
-如果他们跑了怎么办?——在哪里?
- What if they run? - Where?
出城只有一条路。
There's only one way out of town.
侦察员会看到他们的。
The spotters will see them.
所以现在，我们就坐着等待吧。
So now, we just sit back and we play the waiting game.
-他想让我知道什么?
- What was it he wanted me to know?
-他是谁的真相
- The truth about who he was.
中央情报局派了一个叫安东尼的人去杀他们。
The CIA sent a man named Anthony to kill them.
他们说他们是叛徒，把证人的情报卖给俄国人。
They said that they were traitors selling witnesses' intel to the Russians.
-中情局为什么要这么做?
- Why would the CIA do that?
-他们老了。
- They were getting old.
他们太强大了，知道的太多了。
They were too powerful, and they knew too much.
——操!
- Fuck!
-凯勒躲起来了
- Caleb went into hiding.
我父亲中枪了。
My father had been shot.
安东尼的弟弟被杀了。
And Anthony's brother had been killed.
-所以安东尼会来这里?
- So Anthony will come here?
-我希望如此。
- I fucking hope so.
——好。
- Good.
你有什么计划吗?
Do you have a plan?
-我正在研究。
- I'm working on one.
-跟我来。
- Come with me.
这个会有帮助吗?
Will this help?
-他都留着?
- He kept all these?
-他有信任问题。
- He had trust issues.
幸运的我。
Lucky me.
我们应该去楼上。这对我们有利。
We should take the upstairs. It'll be to our advantage.
-我爸爸说如果你不能移动，你就死定了。
- My dad said if you aren't mobile, you're dead.
-通常情况下是这样的。
- Normally, that's true.
但如果我们走，他们会找到我们的。
But if we go anywhere, they'll find us.
这房子是我们的地盘。
This house is our territory.
这对我们有利。
It's advantageous to us.
-他们不会把我们烧光吗?——没有。
- Won't they just burn us out? - No way.
他们需要凯勒的尸体作为杀人的证据。
They need Caleb's body as proof of kill.
有人悬赏我的人头，所以他们也会想要我的。
I have a price on my head, so they'll wanna collect that too.
-你有多少?
- How many you got?
——足够。
- Enough.
-让他们进来。
- Send them in.
-他到底是什么样的人?
- What was he really like?
——什么?
- What?
——我的爸爸。他到底是什么样的人?
- My dad. What was he really like?
-我想你最了解他。
- I think you probably knew him best.
你只是认识另一个版本的他。
You just knew a different version of him.
-你知道哪个版本?
- Which version did you know?
我认识那个高大强壮的混蛋凯勒。
I knew the big, strong, I'm-a-bad-ass Caleb.
他有坚硬的外壳，但是…他对某些人有好感。
He had a hard shell, but... he had a soft spot for a few people.
-你失去父母是什么感觉?
- What was it like when you lost your parents?
-很难。
- It was hard.
我很生气。
I was angry.
但我只是低调行事，专注于工作，专注于回报。
But I just kept my head down, focused on the work, and eye on the prize.
-所以他真的没提过我们?
- So he really never mentioned us?
——没有。
- No.
也就是说他爱你胜过一切。
Which means he loved you more than anything.
他在保护你的安全即使是在他最信任的人面前。
He was protecting your safety even from the ones that he trusted the most.
-所以你猜现在只有我们了?
- So you guess it's just us now?
——是的。
- Yes.
——这很好。
- That's fine.
有点像你。
Kinda like you.
-有点像你。
- Kinda like you too.
-他们为什么不出去?
- Why are they not getting out?
——来到这里。
- Come here.
-你在干什么?
- What are you doing?
-他们用的是热能。我们需要注册为一个。
- They're using thermal. We need to register as one.
-前门好像被钉上了。
- Looks like the front door is boarded up.
——对讲机。
- Walkie.
绕到后面去。
Go around the back.
确保它是一样的。
Make sure it's the same.
——收到。
- Roger that.
-两个男人穿过院子。
- Two guys across the yard.
-后门也被封死了。
- Back door's boarded up too.
-他们把它封起来就走了吗?
- Did they just board it up and leave?
-我只看到一张热成像，所以你他妈在说什么?
- All I'm seeing is one thermal image, so what the fuck are you talking about?
楼下有生命迹象吗?
- Is there any sign of life downstairs?
- 没有。我绕到后面去。
- Negative. I'll go around back.
-长官，如果这是个陷阱呢?
- Sir, what if it's a trap?
-这当然是个陷阱
- Of course it's a trap.
但我得知道第二个人是谁。
But I need to know who the second person is.
趁凯勒还没上节目，用这个查清楚。
Use this to find out before Caleb's on.
是时候了。
It's time.
——嘿,女妖!
- Hey, Banshee!
小婊子!小婊子!
Little bitch! Little bitch!
时间玩!
Time to play!
来吧,女妖。
Come on, Banshee.
我知道你在里面。
I know you're in there.
-小丹，别担心我!
- D, don't worry about me!
杀了这个混蛋!
Kill this bastard!
——女妖……你真的要让你儿子死吗?
- Banshee... are you really going to let your boy die?
——做点什么。
- Do something.
——我不能。
- I can't.
安东尼是唯一知道我父亲的人。
Anthony's the only one who knows about my father.
——哦!
- Oh!
后面还有三个人。
Three more in the back.
走了。
Go.
-三个在后面!他们进来!
- Three going around back! They're coming in!
-哦，该死的!
- Oh, fucking Christ!
匆忙的房子!匆忙的房子!
Rush the house! Rush the house!
-最近怎么样?
- How's it going?
——太棒了!
- Not great!
他妈的没用。
Fucking useless.
他们一直在踢他们，然后他们就走了!
They keep kicking them before they go off!
-煮熟-什么
- Cook 'em. - What?
-煮手榴弹。
- Cook 'the grenades.
-我不知道那是什么意思!
- I don't know what that means!
-扔之前先握几秒钟。
- Hold them for a few seconds before you throw them.
-一，二，三…
- One, two, three...
-你有枪吗?
- You got a gun?
你现在所做的。
You do now.
来吧。
Come on.
-有五六个进来了!
- Five or six coming in!
-盯着安东尼?-我不知道!
- Eyes on Anthony? - I don't know!
他们都戴着面具!
They're all wearing masks!
-那混蛋想拖垮我们。
- Fucker's trying to wear us down.
现在上楼。
Go upstairs now.
他妈的!
Fuck!
——走吧。走，走，走，走!
- Go. Go, go, go, go!
——最后。
- Finally.
——滚蛋。
- Fuck off.
你还有活着的人吗?
Do you got any men left alive?
-我不知道。我想他们都死了。
- I don't know. I think they're all dead.
-不，我做不到
- No, I can't do this.
-你当然可以。
- Of course you can.
听我的。
Listen to me.
我们在那栋楼里找到的人，都要活捉。
Who we find in that building, I want them alive.
你是认真的吗?
- Are you serious?
-我是认真的。
- Yeah, I'm serious.
在我把它们放进尸袋之前，我是认真的。
Until I put them in body bags, I'm very serious.
走了。
Go.
他妈的。
Fuck.
——哇!
- Whoa!
哇。
Wow.
看看你，姑娘。
Look at you, girl.
好工作。
Good job.
迦勒在哪儿?
Where's Caleb?
走,走,走!
Go, go, go!
迦勒在哪儿?
Where's Caleb?
-我有个主意。
- I have an idea.
把你的男人从那女孩身上拿开怎么样?
How about you get your fucking dudes off the girl?
我告诉你凯勒在哪里，你告诉我我父亲在哪里，大家就皆大欢喜了。
I'll tell you where Caleb is, you tell me where my father is, everybody's fucking happy.
-我不记得你父亲在哪了。
- I don't recall where your father is.
-你是个骗子。
- You're a liar.
你知道吗?你是对的。
You know what? You're right.
我确实记得。
I do recall.
我最后一次见他的时候，有几个人把他打得屁滚尿流。
The last time I seen him, there was a couple of guys beating the shit out of him.
他躺在血泊中。
And he was lying in a pool of blood.
愚蠢的我。
Silly me.
-他妈的给我进来!
- Get the fuck in here!
-对一个十几岁的女孩来说有点多了!
- Feels like a little much for a teenage girl!
-他们没找到尸体
- They never found a body.
-或者因为你父亲是个叛徒，他跑了。
- Or because your father's a traitor, and he ran away.
——是错误的。把它们从那该死的女孩身上拿开!
- Wrong. Get them off the fucking girl!
——迦勒在哪儿?
- Where's Caleb?
-埋在后院里。
- Buried in the back yard.
-现在你让我生气了，因为我知道你在撒谎!
- Now you're upsetting me because I know you're lying!
因为凯勒杀了我的人后，我知道他回来了。
'Cause after Caleb shot my men, I know he came back here.
他他妈的在哪儿?
Where the fuck is he?
-你觉得很难受?
- Oh, you're feeling tough?
好吧。
Okay.
我们用老办法吧。
Let's do this old school.
——她开枪!
- Shoot her!
她开枪!
Shoot her!
-是的。嘿,嘿,嘿。
- Yeah. Hey, hey, hey.
在那里……他妈的……是……迦勒?
Where... the fuck... is... Caleb?
嗯?
Huh?
-你出拳像个小贱人。
- You punch like a little fucking bitch.
嘿,混蛋。
- Hey, asshole.
去你妈的。
Fuck you.
——操。
- Fuck.
-还有吗?
- Are there more?
-我希望不是。
- I hope not.
-我今天中枪了。
- I got shot today.
-我也中枪了。
- I got shot too.
——没有。我被击中。
- No. I got shot.
在肩膀上。
In the shoulder.
-只是皮肉伤。你会好的。
- It's a flesh wound. You'll be okay.
- - - - - -接下来是什么?
- What's next?
会有更多的人向我们开枪吗?
Are more people gonna shoot at us?
——可能。
- Probably.
这取决于我们去哪里，去找谁。
It just depends on where we go and who we go after.
但现在，我们还是去酒店房间喝杯鸡尾酒，吃块牛排吧。
But for now, let's just get a cocktail and a steak in a hotel room.
-我没什么想做的。
- There's nothing I'd rather do.
♪我没有家♪
- ♪ I have no home ♪
♪我无处可去
♪ I have nowhere to be ♪
♪我是一个彷徨的人
♪ I'm a wanderer ♪
♬那是我
♪ That's me ♪
♬我不在乎你怎么评价我
♪ And I don't care how you judge me ♪
♪我不在乎你怎么看我
♪ I don't care what you think of me ♪
没有♪♪
♪ No ♪
♬有黑暗♬
♪ There is darkness ♪
♬而雨正倾盆而下
♪ And the rain is pouring down ♪
♬身边到处都是暴力
♪ There is violence all around ♪
♪我也不需要你抱着我
♪ And I don't need you to hold me ♪
♪我不需要你来照顾我
♪ I don't need you to take care of me ♪
没有♪♪
♪ No ♪
♬你想要什么?♪
♪ So what do you want? ♪
♬你现在想从我这里得到什么?♪
♪ What do you want from me now? ♪
♪你伤不了我，没有♪
♪ You can't hurt me, no ♪
♬你也帮不了我
♪ And you can't help me out ♪
♬我会像女妖一样尖叫
♪ And I will scream like a banshee ♪
♬我会像女鬼一样尖叫
♪ I will scream like a banshee ♪
♬你想要什么?♪
♪ So what do you want? ♪
♬你现在想从我这里得到什么?♪
♪ What do you want from me now? ♪
♪你改变不了我，没有♪
♪ You can't change me, no ♪
♬你也不能把我拴住
♪ And you can't chain me down ♪
♬我会像女鬼一样尖叫
♪ I will scream like a banshee ♪
♪我会拼，你挡不住我
♪ I will fight, you can't block me ♪
♪我没有恐惧，你不会阻止我
♪ I have no fear, you won't stop me ♪
♪我一定会赢，你赢不了我
♪ I will win, you can't beat me ♪